

seba2610@gmail.com (+598) 99 50 91 52 Montevideo, Uruguay <u>Linked-In</u> <u>seba2610.github.io</u>

#### PRIMARY SKILLS



.Net Technologies



Node-Js Technologies



**Data Bases** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish

Native

English

Oral, reading & writing

#### SPECIFIC SKILLS

C# NodeJS
.Net Core JavaScript
MVC.NET HTML
Razor CSS

Angular Bootstrap
Typescript NPM
SQL Server jQuery
Git Webpack
Azure PostgresSQL

# Sebastián Caggiano

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



# PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I've more than 13 years of experience working as a developer. Programming and approaching technical challenges, are the things that I love to do the most.

Mentoring and helping my teammates from a technical perspective, is something that I always pursue as a team member.

My main goal is always trying to keep up-to-date working with great technologies, and new ways to do things.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# NodeJS Full-Stack Developer, <u>INumerix</u>

08/2019 - Currently

Development for oil production & oil forecasting web apps.

# .Net Full-Stack Developer, Sonda

10/2010 - 12/2019

Multiple desktop, web apps & services involving emergencies & video security.

## .Net & Web Trainer, Plan Ceibal

05/2017 - 12/2021

Trainer of different courses for web programming using native HTML5, JS, CSS & MVC.NET.



## **ACADEMIC DEGREES**

## **Computer Science Engineer**

Universidad de la República Oriental del Uruguay 2007- 2016

## **Full English Career & First Certificate (ECCE)**

Alianza Uruguay - Estados Unidos 2001-2007

## Front End Developer Certificate (link)

FreeCodeCamp.org

2016